In Return of the Ancients, we're adding
在“远古回归”赛季中，我们将
a set of challenges for the first time
首次
to a POE2 League. Every two challenges
在 POE2 赛季中加入一系列挑战。 每完成两项挑战，你
you complete will give you a piece of
就能获得一件
the Knight of Alder armor set, so it's
阿尔德骑士套装的部件，所以
worth giving them a shot. To check out
值得一试。 要查看
your progression and requirements to
您的进度和
complete a challenge, just hit H to open
完成挑战的要求，只需按 H 键即可
up the challenger screen. There are
打开挑战者屏幕。
eight challenges in all, and they
总共有八项挑战，难度
progress from pretty easy to pretty
由易到难
hard. To complete the rune seeker,
。 要完成符文探索者任务，
you'll need to find remnants with an
你需要找到带有
ever growing number of slots and use
越来越多插槽的残骸，并用
them to craft new items. The seven slot
它们来制作新物品。 七槽
crafts can be pretty challenging with
战舰可能会面临
six waves of enemies, so attempting one
六波敌人的挑战，因此尝试挑战
of these fights could require some
其中一场战斗可能需要一些
skill.
技巧。
Throughout the campaign, there are many
整个战役过程中，有很多
optional bosses. To complete the hunter,
可选的 Boss 战。 要完成猎人任务，
you will need to hunt down six of them.
你需要猎杀其中六个。
The last two, Aki the final sting, and
最后两个，阿基（最后的刺）和
Anund the sandworm, can be pretty tough
阿努德（沙虫），
to find being in the Kari crossing. In
在卡里渡口很难找到。
order to track them down, follow the dry
为了找到它们，沿着干涸的
riverbed. You'll find their arena at the
河床走。 他们的竞技场在
end.
尽头。
The ascendant requires you to gain all
升华需要你
eight points of your ascendency class by
通过升华试炼获得升华职业的全部八个技能点
doing ascendency trials. Getting the
。 不过，要拿到
final set of points can be pretty
最终的分数可能相当具
challenging though. You'll either need
有挑战性。 你要么需要
to defeat Zerok on the fourth level of
在西姆斯试炼的第四关击败泽洛克，要么需要
trial master from the trial of chaos by
在混沌试炼中
finding all three keys. Of the two, the
找到全部三把钥匙来击败试炼大师。 两者之中，
trial of chaos will take you much longer
混乱试炼会花费你更长的时间，
due to having to run the trial multiple
因为你需要多次进行试炼
times. But the trial the second is more
。 但第二次审判更具
challenging. So you'll have to decide
挑战性。 所以你必须决定
which of these two paths to take.
走这两条路中的哪一条。
The reoquarian is simple. Identify 50
雷奥夸里安很简单。 找出 50 种
different unique items.
不同的独特物品。
Having a tough time finding uniques?
找不到独特的商品？
Jado the Atlas master has a lot of
阿特拉斯大师杰多拥有许多
abilities that specialize in finding
专门寻找
them.
它们的能力。
To complete the artisan, you'll need to
要完成工匠职业，你需要
use a bunch of different crafting items,
使用许多不同的制作材料，这些材料都
all of which come from remnant
来自遗迹
encounters.
遭遇战。
For the ctographer, you'll need to
对于 ctographer，您需要
allocate your entire atlas tree, all 300
分配整个图谱树，即所有 300 个
nodes. You can do this the slow way by
节点。 你可以慢慢来，把
fortress. But there's another way, too.
要塞内的所有地图都探索完。 但还有另一种方法。
Each time you defeat the Arbiter of
每次击败
Divinity, you'll gain the ability to
神明仲裁者，你都将获得
automatically complete a large section
自动完成要塞很大一部分的能力
of the fortress.
。
citadels in the Atlas. Each of them have
在地图集中寻找要塞，找到他战斗的关键。 它们各自发出
big glowing beams so you can see them in
巨大的发光光束，因此即使在雾中也能看到它们
the fog. After fighting him four times,
。 与他战斗四次后，
the entire fortress will be completed.
整个要塞就会建成。
And last, but certainly not least, the
最后，但同样重要的是，
Vanquisher. This challenge requires
征服者。 这项挑战需要
killing three pinnacle bosses, the
击败三个巅峰首领，这是
hardest fights in the game. Tangazu, the
游戏中难度最高的战斗。 唐加祖、
Bodark, and the Vessel of Coolark. These
博达克和库拉克之器。 这些分别
are the pinnacles of Delarium, Ritual,
是 Delarium、Ritual
and Abyss Leagues. So, you'll need to do
和 Abyss 联赛的巅峰之作。 所以，你需要完成
these three quest lines in order to do
这三条任务线才能完成
this challenge. One important thing with
这个挑战。
the Vessel of Coolark, though, is you
不过，对付库拉克之器，有一点很重要，那就是你
need to defeat him at full strength.
必须在它全盛时期击败它。
That means risking the item during the
这意味着在与
boss fight by returning the finger and
Boss 战斗时，要冒着失去道具的风险，将手指还给 Boss，然后
defeating him anyway.
仍然击败他。
Now, as I said before, every two
正如我之前所说，每
challenges you complete will get you
完成两项挑战，你就能获得
pieces of the armor set, so you don't
套装部件，所以你
have to do all of them to get some
不必完成所有挑战就能获得一些
rewards. But if you do, you'll be able
奖励。 但如果你这样做，你就可以
to show off your prowess because
炫耀你的实力，因为
everyone in global chat or in the forums
全球聊天室或论坛中的每个人都
can see how many challenges you've
可以看到你赢得了多少挑战
earned. You'll also get this totem
。 你还将获得这个图腾
decoration for your hideout, meaning the
装饰品，可以放在你的藏身处，这意味着
forever more people who trade with you
以后所有与你交易的人
will be able to see that you were there
都能看到你曾到过那里，
and you defeated the league. Try out
并且击败了联盟。
these challenges and more on May 29th in
5月29日，在《远古回归》中体验这些挑战以及更多精彩内容
Return of the Ancients. Thanks for
。 感谢
watching and see you then.
收看，我们下次再见。